Nice, Sumi-chan! Up high!
That was fun.
Don't forget the kissy face, Sumi-chan!
I thought I was good at going it alone
Would you prefer to go together?
Place
your finger here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
"Long Time No Girlfriend"
Gah, I can't! It's been two days
since we got back to Tokyo,
and I keep thinking about that kiss,
all day and all night!
This has to be
some kind of curse!!
My world's been dyed pink ever since.
dazed
My brain must be completely broken.
It not like that was
the first time, right?
Mizuhara and I actually kissed.
You could write off the first time as CPR.
But this was totally a kiss.
Kiss is. Kiss is in-itself.
Kiss is what it is.
Not again!
Embrace the kiss
I can't eat or do my assignments!
The hard disk of my brain is being overwritten bit by bit!
Am I gonna be like this
for the rest of my life?!
Wait, calm down.
Don't trip out
again!!
You also put her on the spot.
Settle down and think this through.
Hear me out, Mizuhara!
I'm sorry.
She knew I was gonna ask her out, right?
Still... she kissed me! To help me out.
That's like...
Mm
Smooch
I love you, too!
That's like giving me the green light!
The eyes of a shoplifter
No, wait!
Did she really know? There's a chance she
didn't catch on to what I was gonna do!
That'd mean she really did help me
out of the goodness of her heart!
And what she said
after that was true
Who are you telling to wait over and over?
Kindness
But remember, she asked if I was trying
to pop some kind of question!
What else could she have meant there?
Is there some other kind of question
to pop that I'm simply not aware of?
guy girl the talk
The merits of working up the courage to pop the question
I figured not. It had to be
about me asking her out, right?
But it's hard to tell what goes
through Mizuhara's head sometimes!
Wait, what? Where did all this come from?
I seriously can't believe you.
What if I try to ask her out again,
eek
and she acts like it
came out of nowhere?
Mizuhara's seriously an enigma.
Love Neurosis
Gimme a top-secret gadget
that lets me read her mind.
Even after we split off from
the group at Ueno Station...
I need to stop by somewhere.
I'll take a different route home
See you.
S-Sure.
R-Ruka-chan?!
Hey, that hurt.
You deserve to feel at least 1%
of the pain you put me through!
Also, get away
from him!!
Listen, I'll say what happened
this time doesn't count.
The most special
of exceptions!!
That it was a necessary evil to
protect my boyfriend's reputation.
But you need to remember where you stand!
You're a rental girlfriend.
You shouldn't be getting
on any trains with a client.
Wait, Ruka-chan.
I'm the one to blame here.
You're not off the hook either!
nag nag
You got a golden opportunity to
come clean, and you just wasted it!
Do you realize that?!
I wouldn't call it "golden."
But that's what it was!
Sorry.
I'm kind of in a hurry.
Heck, she was
even kinda standoffish
Ruka-chan's alarm bells were going off,
but Mizuhara was just acting normal.
How could she stay so calm
after all that happened?
Does she have ice in
her veins or something?
That was a kiss! She kissed you, dude!
But he was right.
You can make all the excuses
for it you want,
but going back to normal after that
just doesn't make any sense at all.
Besides, I'm this close to going insane.
It's not about logic or reason anymore.
Tell me, Mizuhara.
How do you feel about everything?
Was that kiss purely to help me out?
Nothing more than that?
I wanna see her. I wanna see
her face. I wanna hear her voice.
I can't control myself anymore.
She can't be in class this early.
Yoga
Free Trial!!
Saved this mistakenly
delivered mail for
a time like this
I firmly believe we are in need of
conversation at this moment!
Ichinose
It's all good.
Worst case, I just came
to hand over the mail.
And if she's in a good mood,
I'll make some small talk...
and then ask her if she
wants to chat a little.
Screw it!
No response?!
tremble tremble
I don't hear a peep.
Is she out this early?
If she didn't want me calling on her,
she'd just come out yelling at me.
I've been chasing
my own tail again
Aw, man.
She's out, huh?
Eh, whatever. I'll come back another time.
Huh?
I just heard something.
Does that mean she's home?
Then why isn't she responding?
O-One more time.
Face naturally
turns into this
Glaring match
with the doorknob
Why is she still not answering?
I know I sensed her in there!
Or was it just my imagination?
I can't talk to her through the opening.
That'd be a repeat of that one time.
A dark chapter
of his life
Yeah, let's just say
I was imagining things.
Man...
I can't take this.
Yoga
Free Trial!!
Did I really just imagine that, though?
I don't know why,
but I feel like she's home.
I can feel
her in there
Even more so after hearing
that noise back there.
Why didn't she answer, then?
That'd mean she faked not being home...
Because she didn't want to see me.
Wait, why?
doooom
Why would she do that?
Did I do something to piss her off?
There's only one thing I can think of
after everything that happened.
She's totally mad at me!
I even had to kiss you
because of this mess you created!
I'm taking legal action now, so just
wait at home until you get served!
Argh! She was being all nice,
Duh! She had to
kiss a guy like me!!
but deep down, she hated it all!
And she lied to me to get away from me!
Did she wash her mouth
out thoroughly later?
splash splash
Gah! I could die right now!
I could ascend
or descend!!
I could die internally from the guilt
and the massive blow to my self-esteem!
But..
But...
But!
Mizuhara, I can't take this.
Even if I know I'm being a bother, I'm in
no state to give up on you anymore.
One message wouldn't be too weird, right?
Heya! Some yoga pamphlet addressed to you got delivered
to me instead. Should I slip it through your mail slot?
Keep it natural.
I'm just sounding her out. It's not like
I'm asking her on a date or anything.
You keep using
the yoga thing!
Actually, should I say
"put" instead of "slip"?
Phrasing is important.
But should I avoid being too businesslike
and keep it casual? Which is it?
The most irrelevant dilemma of all time!
Would this be my first time texting
her outside the movie thing?
What if she thinks
I'm pushing my luck?!
It's much harder to do this for idle talk!
Screw it!
Don't chicken out! Don't chicken out!
I mean, she wouldn't be checking
her phone at this exact moment.
If she couldn't even answer the door,
she must be really bu—
Read
...sy!
Fast!!
Read receipt!
Mizuhara checked it! Is she home?
Is she bored?
Wait, she could've checked it anywhere.
And that doesn't even matter!
Read
Is she typing now?
Ichinose Chizuru
Read
I should take a bath!
Not that
she can see
Yeah, it'd gross her out if I just
sat here waiting for her to reply!
But I'm like
some kinda stalker
Heya! Some yoga pamphlet addressed to you got delivered
to me instead. Should I slip it through your mail slot?
Read
gloom
I guess she's really busy!
Play rehearsals, maybe?
She might have a backlog
of class assignments
Well, duh. I rang her doorbell,
and she couldn't even answer that!
Time to sleep!
Night!
Or she might be sick! Hope she's okay!
Grown-ups say communication and
romance are instant in this day and age.
You can pay money to be
a pretty girl's "boyfriend,"
and you can be connected to
your beloved in a few seconds.
When, then, will this pain instantly pass?
Got it. Thanks for that.
After we came back from Hawaiians...
Since November 25,
two days after we kissed...
Got it. Thanks for that.
Chi-chan, rehearsal's starting.
Oh, sorry.
Even the super-wary Ruka-chan
had nothing to worry about.
Because, for a period of three months,
I couldn't get in touch
with Mizuhara once.
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Yes?
That's my master!
Is that cosplay?!
Are you a shut-in who hasn't bathed
in two weeks for Halloween?
Halloween was quite
a while ago, though
Bahut dino se mulakat nahi!
(Long time no see!)
Oh, it's just you.
You should stop acting like anyone other
than Mizuhara-san is a disappointment.
What do you mean,
"just" me?
Th-That's not what I meant...
Your face is as red as
the Lal Qila, the Red Fort.
What even is that?
Bahut?
I was away on a trip to India!
For a month
I'd love to chat,
but I'm sleeping right now.
Huh?
Wha...
Th-This is bad!
Wh-What's wrong, Master?
Did something happen with Mizuhara-san?
Master!
Hang in there!
I love him because he never
forgets to feed me at least.
You kissed?!
Y-Yeah...
Wha...
Then what are you doing here?
Why aren't you buried in her bosom?!
What're you talking about?
That kiss was an "I love you"!
Nobody'd bat an eyelid if you'd
flown to Paris right after!
Like I said...
Mizuhara only did that to help me
because Mami-chan demanded we kiss.
She put herself
on the line
Uh, are you stupid?!
Stu—
What are you even saying? That she
kissed you without having any feelings?
Are you okay with her being a slut
who uses a kiss as a get-out-of-jail card?
Wha... Of course not!
There's no way she doesn't
feel anything for you!
You're making a mockery
of Mizuhara-san!
We've reached a point where not
asking her out would be insulting!
I'm so happy...
I'm so happy for you!
Sheesh, this girl.
She never changes
Wait.
Th-Then why's your apartment a pig sty?
This makes zero sense
I haven't heard from her in three months.
She left me on read, too.
She totally hates me now.
Wha?
fingerprints
She's got free
slots, though
I even tried renting her out,
but I keep getting told she's booked.
She's clearly avoiding me.
What?
No renting, either
Why?
That makes no sense
That's what I'd like to know!
But it's okay!
It doesn't change the fact that
it's okay to believe in yourself!
Huh?
I mean, you asked her out, right?
Huh? I... I guess?
I'd say that's
what that was
That means she did that
knowing you had a thing for her!
She could've put
an end to it,
but she couldn't
control her feelings
Even the fact that you were rental GF
and client is wind in your sails!
Then why'd she ghost me for three months?
That, I don't know!
Why're you so confident, then?!
Anyway, if she said she kissed you
"for work," that'd weird me out!
Boys be ambitious
Even Mizuhara-san
knows that
There must be some kind
of reason for all this!
It's only a matter of time before
the fortress falls! No, it wants to fall!
Gah! Even if you're right,
I can't anymore!
Nobody's busy for three months!
She hates me! I know she does!
Untrue! She's probably touching her lips
and grinning to herself about now!
That's not Mizuhara! She's the ice queen
who can act in her everyday life!
No more pain!!
I don't wanna be
hurt anymore!!
His drill of persecution
is piercing the heavens.
Never mind. I'll make hotpot.
It's over. No matter what
Yaemori-san says, I have no faith.
I know it's a valuable
girl's POV, but...
If I can't even rent her out, that means
she doesn't even want to talk to me.
What else can I do?
If, after breaking rules, asking her out,
getting rejected, and being avoided,
I rang her doorbell and
still tried to approach her...
I'd just be a stalker, wouldn't I?
And it turns out they actually kissed.
But they lost contact after that,
so my friend has no idea what to do.
I wanna cheer them up so bad
They kissed, right? It's a lock, then
This friend of yours is leading
quite an entertaining life lol
They should go for it
Yeah, you think so too, right?
Ichinose
She's not answering? I guess
she realized I'm part of his crew.
Is she avoiding me?
The lights are off.
Surely she wouldn't turn them
off to pretend she's out.
I'll go to the
convenience store
I simply can't believe the Mizuhara-san
I know would kiss someone for no reason.
But three months is a long time, yeah.
Of course it'd make Master all anxious.
Did she really come to hate him?
grab
You're not getting away!
What?!
Sorry.
And it's hot,
to boot
All I have is barley tea.
Oh, that's no problem at all.
It was chilly outside
I actually got into her apartment.
I did not see that coming.
I thought she was wary of me
because I was part of Master's crew.
She's more welcoming than a girl who's
ghosted him for three months should be.
We both need to watch our weight,
so no need for snacks, right?
Right.
I didn't expect this, though.
Acting like a fool
I figured you saw me as
a part of Master's crew.
sweatdrop
I do think you two are friends.
But I have no reason to
give you the cold shoulder.
Sounds like I can ask her
a bunch of questions.
Master's totally down in the dumps
because he can't get in touch with you.
I'm not going to make excuses.
I do think that was crappy of me.
I heard what happened.
Oh, it's not like he blabbed.
I forced it out of him.
About what happened at Hawaiians,
and how you two went through a lot.
I cheered him up
a little for you
Of course you'd want to take
a step back and take stock.
But still, why are you avoiding him?
I don't regret it or anything.
If I went back to that moment,
I'd still do the same thing.
I'm legitimately
Kazuya-san's girlfriend now.
But that went way beyond
the rental girlfriend thing,
and I know I was dishonest
with his family.
It's my fault for never doing the right
thing for my client, despite being a pro.
That's not an answer.
Why exactly are you avoiding Master?
Ruka-chan.
Huh?
I really hurt Ruka-chan.
I was the one who got them together.
If this is what being wishy-washy led to,
then I need to put a stop to it.
So she chose to distance herself?
But it's so like her to be
straight as an arrow.
But, hey, that's unavoidable
if you both like each other.
Even I don't know why I'm doing this.
What?
I mean it when I say I don't regret it.
I'd do the same thing every time.
But what I don't get is,
even with Ruka-chan right there,
what made me want to
defend him so badly?
I don't know what to call these feelings.
I can't explain them to her.
It's love! That's what they're called!
I figured you'd say that,
but it's not that cut and dry.
What are you talking about?
It's clear as day!
Don't you start thinking
about him out of nowhere?
Doesn't his face come up when you
look at a carrot or something?
Don't you get all warm and fuzzy
inside when you think about him?
Whoa, whoa.
You may be trying to hold
back because of your job,
but sometimes it just won't work!
You're a wonderful person!
There's no need for you to talk
yourself down as a rental girlfriend!
I truly believe how nice you've been
to Master is a show of your character!
But are you sure you're not
just running away right now?!
Or just using your job as an excuse to
put your feelings out of sight and mind?!
If you don't understand how you feel,
that's all the more reason to talk it out!
Ghosting him is the worst possible move!
But doing that over and over is
what got us here to begin with.
We've come so far, there's no going back.
I'm saying there's no reason to!
Ruka-chan's the one who's truly in love.
She has no qualms about wearing her heart
on her sleeve and expressing herself.
I can't get in the way of her love
when I don't even know how I feel.
I'm even kind of envious of
how passionate she can get.
I get that, but it's not always
that simple and obvious.
Anyway, I can't bear to see the state
Master's in! Please get in touch with him!
I get what you're saying.
But if that's your reason after he even
asked you out, I'd say that's mean!
Master started to dream! And I feel like
you're ready to make it come true!
Please, face his feelings head-on!
That's all I can say.
Thanks for the tea
I'll just grab your panties and head out.
Uh, why exactly?
Is Master out?
The lights are out
It'd be good for him
to step outside
every now and then
I'll tell him tomorrow.
I saw it coming, but Mizuhara-san...
She's gone past "too serious"
and into "huge pain" territory.
Things should actually work out
for them if all goes well...
I said what I had to, but who knows
if my words actually reached her?
Viewership retention's
on the brink, y'know?
These two are
such a handful
All right!
Okay, thanks for having me.
Hey! Don't just take my panties!
I-It's not what you think!
It's my fate as a streamer!
Please overlook it!
Streaming's got nothing to do with it!
Eek! Help! Mizuhara-san's
gonna take my panties!
Don't frame me! Those are mine!
Just give them back!
No, Mizuhara-san! Not there!
Move on already! Next time
on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Valentine's and...
...Girlfriend."
Can I profile these panties in a video?
"Valentine's and Girlfriend"
Not in a million years!